KIRILL TARASOV

Russia, Moscow · +7 (910) 763 07 83 tarasowkirill@gmail.com · k5ta.github.io

My experience in the industry is quite diverse: architectural design and application implementation, deployment and monitoring, team leadership and communication with customers. I easily master new material and am not afraid of non-trivial tasks, since exactly these things that help to develop into much more.

EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2020 – UP TO PRESENT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, CYBERTONICA

Backend part of the fraud monitoring system development, customer integration implementation. Experience exchanging and training other employees. Communication with internal, external customers and other teams, participation in product tasks creation.

FEBRUARY 2018 - OCTOBER 2020

TEAM LEAD AND SOFTWARE ENGINEER, INFORION

Development of ETL applications for working with large amounts of data. Implementation of research tasks. Conducting workshops and mentoring for new employees. Leading the development team, forming sprints and prioritizing tasks, communicating with customers and updating product requirements.

JUNE 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, SPACETY

SPA development using Vue.js and React. Sites commissioning, testing and support. Communication with customers and designers.

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2015 – JUNE 2021

COMPUTER SECURITY, BAUMAN MOSCOW STATE TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

Information security specialist (specialization – mathematical methods of information security). Diploma with honors, GPA is 5.0. Field of scientific interests – image recognition and generation.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Scala, Java, Python, JavaScript
- ELK, TICK, MongoDB, ClickHouse
- Puppet, Teamcity, Gitlab CI/CD
- Git, Mercurial
- Jira, Confluence, Redmine, Wekan
- Team management and ability to work in it
- Tasks setting, decomposition and delegation
- Time management
- Negotiating, ability to listen others opinion and arguing mine
- Upper-Intermediate English

OTHER INTERESTS

- The winner of the Voluntary qualification examination (DKE) in 2019
- Interests economics, different variations of traveling, badminton